nuvo.net 2006-06-21

# nuvo.net / privacy policy

As of 11/05/05

A detailed privacy policy follows, but the bottom line is this: NUVO will not sell or share any of your personal information to a third party unless you say it's okay. NUVO will gather personally identifiable information about you only when you provide it voluntarily for specific purposes such as posting an ad or signing up for an e-mail newsletter. Be a well-informed nuvo.net user by reading the details below, and check back regularly for updates.

Thank you for visiting Nuvo.net (the "Site"), a Nuvo, Inc. website. At NUVO ("NUVO", "us", "we", or "our"), we recognize and respect the importance of maintaining your privacy. We have established this Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") to inform you of the kinds of information we may gather during your visit to the Site, why we gather customer information, what we use the information for, under what circumstances we may disclose such information, and how you can instruct us to limit the use of that information.

**By visiting the Site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site and exit immediately. We reserve the right to modify or amend the terms of this Privacy Policy from time to time without notice at any time. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes.**

If you have any questions please [e-mail us](mailto:webmaster@nuvo.net), or write us at 3951 N. Meridian St., Suite 200, Indianapolis, IN 46208 with comments or questions. See [about NUVO](http://www.nuvo.net/misc/about/) to find out more about _NUVO_ and our policies.

**1\. What Information We Gather**  
We do not intentionally collect any personally identifiable information about you except when you provide it.

**_Classified Ads_** :  
When you place a classified ad on our Site, we will ask you for your e-mail address and other information that allows respondents to contact you. We will not share that information with any third party. You can choose to hide your personal information from other Site users.

**_Newsletter_** :  
NUVO collects email addresses and zip codes of all users who subscribe to our weekly newsletter. This information is not shared with any third parties for any purposes. Anyone who wishes to no longer receive this newsletter can, at any time, click on the "Unsubscribe" feature located within each newsletter.

**_Anonymous Use Information:_**  
We do collect anonymous information about all of our users, including the way our users access the Site and the content. We analyze information to determine how our users are making use of various parts of the Site, to improve the Site, and so we can share "rating" information with our partners. This information is typically shared on an aggregated basis and cannot be used to identify individual Users.

**_Giveaways and Contests_**  
If you sign up to be eligible for a giveaway or contest on our Site, your information will be shared with the advertiser or sponsor of that giveaway or contest for one-time use to notify you if you have won. To the extent the giveaway or contest has its own terms that conflict with the terms of this Privacy Policy, the terms of the giveaway or contest shall govern. Personally identifiable information will be collected only if you voluntarily submit it to our sponsors or us.

**_Under 13_** :  
We do not knowingly collect any information from persons under the age of 13\. If we learn that any persons under the age of 13 have provided information about themselves, the information will be deleted. Our Site is designed for adults. Our Site is not intentionally targeted to children under the age of 13.

 _Children under the age of 13 should not use our Site without obtaining prior parental consent_

.

**_Co-Branded Services_ :**  
We work closely with our partners to offer co-branded services such as, the online personals service provided by **Telepublishing International**. For privacy policies governing these types of services, please see the separate privacy policies within these sections. To the extent such policies conflict with the terms of this Privacy Policy, the terms of such other policy shall govern.

**_Links to Other Sites_ :**  
Our Site contains links to other Web sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Please be aware that when you click on links and/or advertisement banners that take you to third-party Web sites, you will be subject to the third parties' privacy policies, not ours. While we support the protection of privacy on the Internet, we are not responsible for the actions and privacy policies of third parties and other Web sites. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement and user terms and conditions whenever interacting with, and prior to providing any personal information to, any other Web site. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by NUVO on this Site.

**2\. How We Use the Information We Gather**  
The information collected is used internally by NUVO for four main purposes: (1) To determine which areas, features, and products our users like the most and find most helpful as part of our continuing efforts to improve our Site; (2) To personalize the Site for our users (for example, if you have indicated an interest in jazz, we may make you aware of upcoming jazz events); (3) To enable our users to participate in sweepstakes, contests, services, and other activities on our Site; and (4) to enable users to place classified advertisements in designated areas of the Site. In all cases described below we will not sell or share any personally identifiable information with any third party without your consent.

When we conduct user surveys to find out how we can improve our Site for you, we may share aggregated non-personal information about our users with advertisers or other third parties. For example, we might disclose that a certain percentage of our users are female.

We also use certain third-party advertising services (including, in particular, Real Media) to display advertising for our advertisers. These third-party services may place a cookie on your computer for the purposes of ad tracking and presentation. (See "Cookies and IP Addresses", below, if you're not sure what a cookie is.)

We occasionally have third party agents, subsidiaries, affiliates and joint ventures that perform functions on our behalf, such as credit card processing, shipping or stocking orders, providing customer service, managing user ids and passwords, etc. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, and are contractually obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of the data. They are restricted from using or altering this data in any way other than to provide the requested services to the Site.

You can choose to electronically forward a story from our Site to a friend by entering the friend's e-mail address. You can also request that we send an email alert when your favorite columnist posts a column or when certain classified ads are posted. We don't sell or share the addresses used in our _E-mail This to a Friend_ service or our alerts to any third-party.

Please remember that any information you share in public areas, such as message boards like [**Forums**](http://www.nuvo.net/forums/) or [**Online Classifieds**](http://www.nuvo.net/classifieds/) sections, becomes public, and therefore this Privacy Policy does not apply to any information you choose to make public. Please be careful about what you disclose and do not post any personal information that you expect to keep private. 

Some of our services require you to register for an account, such as Blogs or the Music Community. We will ask you for some personal information in order to create an account (typically your name, email address and to establish a user id and password for your account) and we will use that information in connection with providing these services.

Please note that whenever you choose to share information in the public areas of the Site, you grant us a license (as described in NUVO's [**Classified Terms of Use**](http://classifieds.nuvo.net/media/termsandconditions.cfm)) to that information you publish. We occasionally will publish or use in connection with promotional and/or marketing materials any posted comments on our Site or feedback received via e-mail (especially if you say nice things about us).

**3\. How We Use "Cookies" and IP Addresses**  
_Cookies:_ When you visit the Site, we send your computer a "cookie," a small data file that's stored on your hard drive. We use cookies to understand Site usage and to give you better, more personalized service. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but you may not be able to take full advantage of our Site's features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on. We do not install, or authorize the installation of, web beacons, web bugs, "single-pixel gifs" or other types of spyware on users' computers.

  **Note:** You will see advertising on our Site that originates with outside advertisers and/or advertising agencies. In some cases, if you click on or view these ads, the advertisers will assign a cookie for ad tracking and presentation purposes. We are not responsible for nor have any control over these cookies.

  _IP address tracking:_ All computers and servers on the Internet use IP addresses to recognize and communicate with each other. _The Voice_ collects IP addresses to administer and analyze our Site and report aggregate, non-personal information (such as how many visitors we have). When you call up our Site on your computer, our servers enter the IP address of that computer into a log. To maintain our users' anonymity, we do not associate IP addresses with records containing personal information.

We do not and cannot use cookies or IP address tracking to retrieve personal information from your computer.

**4\. Additional Circumstances When Information May be Shared**  
In addition to what is stated above, we share customer information only under the following, limited circumstances:

We may disclose personal information if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law or with legal process, protect and defend our rights and property, protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Site or protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide false information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions).

Although your privacy is very important to us, in the existing legal regulatory and security environment, we cannot fully guarantee that your personal information will not be disclosed to third parties. For example, under certain circumstances the government or unrelated third parties might legally require us to disclose information to them, or third parties might unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Additionally, in the unlikely event we need to investigate or resolve possible problems or inquiries, we can (and you authorize us to do so) disclose any information about you to private entities and law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate.

**5\. Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place physical, electronic and managerial procedures to protect the information we collect. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted with secure socket layer (SSL) encryption technology prior to transmission over the Internet.

While we make reasonable efforts to safeguard your personal information once we receive it, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or information we transmit to you from our Site, and you do so at your own risk.

**6\. Governing Law/ Sale of the Company**  
Our Site is a published in the United States. U. S. law shall govern in any and all disputes, including privacy or defamation issues or otherwise.

In the event of a sale of NUVO or a sale of substantially all NUVO's assets, the email database and all user information shall accrue to the new owners. So that the services provided to our users may continue uninterrupted. Any such sales are not anticipated to otherwise alter the basic terms of this Privacy Policy. 

**7\. Changes**  
As our Site continues to develop, we may add new services and features to our Site. In the event that these additions, changes to the law or changes to NUVO policy affect our Privacy Policy, we may change our Privacy Policy from time to time. Please read this Privacy Policy each time you use our Site to be informed of any such changes.
